<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="productName">
        <item>Rahua Hydration Conditioner 9.3oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Voluminous Shampoo 9.3oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Hydration Shampoo 9.3oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Classic Conditioner 9.3oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Voluminous Conditioner 9.3oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Leave-In Treatment 2oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Legendary Amazon Oil 1.6oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Enchanted Island Salt Spray 4.2oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Elixir 1oz</item>
        <item>Rahua Body Oil 2oz</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="productPrice">
        <item>36.00</item>
        <item>34.00</item>
        <item>34.00</item>
        <item>36.00</item>
        <item>36.00</item>
        <item>45.00</item>
        <item>42.00</item>
        <item>32.00</item>
        <item>175.00</item>
        <item>57.00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="productDescription">
        <item>Created to replenish the driest, thirstiest hair, this rich and creamy formula is infused with our plant-powered complex crafted with rare Amazonian oils and natural protein-bonding sugars that drive hydration deep into each strand of hair. Scented with the tropical aromas of passion fruit and mango, this innovative formula softens, de-tangles and tames hair, leaving it manageable and stronger, healthier, smoother and shinier.</item>
        <item>Our award-winning Voluminous Shampoo strengthens, clarifies, and nourishes hair while delivering noticeable volume and body. A combination of green tea antioxidants, citrus juices and lemongrass removes product build-up and reduces oil production to extend time between shampoos—without drying hair or scalp. Rahua oil, rich in omega-9, fortifies hair from within to help prevent breakage and lavender and eucalyptus extracts offer a calm, uplifting aromatherapy experience.</item>
        <item>Created to replenish the driest, thirstiest hair, this rich and creamy formula is infused with our plant-powered complex crafted with rare Amazonian oils and natural protein-bonding sugars that drive hydration deep into each strand of hair. Scented with the tropical aromas of passion fruit and mango, this innovative formula leaves scalp hydrated and balanced and hair stronger, healthier, smoother and shinier.</item>
        <item>An enriching and luxurious complement to our Rahua® Classic Shampoo, this award-winning Conditioner delivers lustrous, rich and ultra-hydrated hair. Omega-9-rich Rahua oil acts as a detangler and exotic extracts maintain strong hair and a healthy scalp. Can also be used as a lightweight styling cream to smooth, tame frizz and flyaways, and add hold.</item>
        <item>A nourishing complement to our Voluminous Shampoo, this rich yet weightless conditioner leaves hair lustrous, silky, and full of body and bounce. Perfect for co-washing, it is enhanced with soothing lavender and uplifting eucalyptus for a transporting aromatherapy experience.</item>
        <item>Protective and healing, this flexible anti-frizz treatment—perfect whether you style with hot tools or air dry—delivers remarkable shine, shields hair from stress, and prevents breakage and split ends. Crafted using omega-9-rich Rahua oil, it acts as a heat protectant, guards hair from the stress of blowdrying and styling tools and adds definition and separation when air drying.</item>
        <item>This exclusive Rahua® blend uses light-as-air plant and flower oils—not silicones—to deliver a beautifully smooth, shiny, anti-frizz finish. Rahua, Sacha Inchi, and Morete oils harvested in the Amazon penetrate deeply into each hair strand to heal and strengthen. A powerful way to banish flyaways, heal split ends, and promote shine, this formula is quick absorbing and remarkably revitalizing. Formulated especially for daily use.</item>
        <item>Inspired by the Galapagos Islands, our Enchanted Island™ Salt Spray offers sexy, tousled, wavy beach hair. Crafted with natural pink sea salt for texture and volume, this spray offers light, brushable hold and the lush, tropical fragrance combination of guayaba, hibiscus, and passion fruit.Your purchase supports The Pink Flamingos Project.</item>
        <item>Crafted with 100 percent pure handmade Rahua oil, this luxurious, concentrated hair and scalp treatment delivers dramatic results. Sustainably harvested in the Amazon rainforest, Rahua oil visibly revitalizes and strengthens weak, damaged strands, leaving hair supremely healthy and naturally radiant, while an infusion of active antioxidants, antibacterials, and microcirculatory properties work together to balance and restore the scalp. Super-fine molecules push color pigmentation deep into the hair shaft, greatly extending color endurance. Naturally scented with the fresh, woodsy aroma of Palo Santo oil, this super-concentrated deep treatment heals, hydrates, and transforms.</item>
        <item>Crafted with potent oils meticulously cultivated in the Amazon rainforest, this delicate mist is surprisingly powerful. Fast-absorbing, lightweight and deeply hydrating, this restorative oil is filled with omega-3 and omega-9 fatty acids, antioxidants, carotenoids, and vitamins C and E, which work to repair, heal, and moisturize dry skin. Highly effective and lightly scented with rainforest botanicals, it delivers luminous, healthy skin.</item>
    </string-array>
    
</resources>